We all know that with the change in the way of life, the number of patients with diabetes is increasing.
The number of patients with diabetes is also increasing.
This has become a global public health problem.
So, high blood pressure, diabetes, and diabetes are often not the same.
If you have a disease that is not well controlled, it will often lead to many diseases.
Just like diabetes, if you don't control it, you will have diabetes.
In some cities, diabetes has become the first disease of the disease.
So, here is also the action of the experts and medical staff to actively participate in the public science and technology.
Let us use the words of the common sense of life.
For more people, we have the knowledge of the disease that brings us to science and technology.
We can also be able to get into early diagnosis and early treatment.
We will eventually form a comprehensive response to help them make comprehensive management.
We will be able to achieve a long-term high blood pressure survival.
The science and technology is a small step.
Health in China is a big step.